http://www.sihlusa.com/privacy.html

Contact Us
Simply the better solution
Products by:
Search by Category
TechnologyDye Sub InksAqueous InkjetLatex InkjetSolvent InkjetUV Curable InkjetDigital Press (DT)
ApplicationsAdvertising & POSDye SublimationInterior DesignPhoto & ArtTechnical Solutions
LEGAL NOTICE/PRIVACY STATEMENT
Sihl Inc.
713 Fenway Avenue, Suite B
Chesapeake, VA 23323
All rights reserved.
Terms of Use
These Terms of Use govern your use and access to this website. We may change, update, delete or add to these terms over time. By accessing and using this website, you agree to these Terms of Use, all policies within this website, and all changes or modifications to the foregoing. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, such policies, or any modifications thereto, please do not use this website.
Privacy Policy Statement
Sihl encourages you to read Sihl’s Privacy Policy Statement so that you may make an informed decision about using this website. Privacy Policy listed below.
Copyright
This website is Copyright Sihl Inc. 2012. All copyrighted and copyrightable materials on this website, including, without limitation, the design, text, artwork, technical documentation, manuals, diagrams, product information, graphics, images, pictures, photographs, sound files and other files ("Materials"), and the selection and arrangement thereof, are owned by Sihl and/or its licensors. No Materials may be copied, imitated or used in any way whatsoever without the prior written permission of Sihl except that Sihl grants to you limited rights to access the website and use the Materials for personal, non-commercial and informational use only provided that the Sihl copyright notice is reproduced therein. This license may not be sub-licensed, assigned or transferred in any manner.
The foregoing license grant does NOT include the right for you to: publish, publicly perform or display, or distribute to any third party any Materials, including reproduction on any computer network or broadcast or publications media; market, sell or make commercial use of this site or any Materials; systematically collect or use any data or content including the use of any data spiders, robots, or similar data gathering, mining or extraction methods; make derivative uses of this site or the Materials; or use, frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any portion of this site (including the images found at this site or any text or the layout/design of any page or form contained on a page).
Except for the limited license granted to you, you are not conveyed any other right or license by implication, estoppel, or otherwise in or under any patent, trademark, copyright, or proprietary right of Sihl or any third party. Any unauthorized use of this Site will terminate the permission or license granted by these Terms of Use and may violate applicable law including copyright laws, trademark laws (including trade dress), and communications regulations and statutes.
Trademarks
"Sihl" and the Sihl logo, and any proprietary product or service names contained in this website are either trademarks or registered trademarks of Sihl or its licensors, and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of Sihl. In addition, all page headers, custom graphics, button icons and scripts are service marks, trademarks and/or trade dress of Sihl and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of Sihl. All other trademarks, registered trademarks, product names and company names or logos mentioned herein are the property of their respective owners.
Accounts and Passwords
You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. Sihl reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts or cancel orders in its sole discretion.
Choice of Law and Jurisdiction
This website is controlled from the Sihl offices located in Chesapeake, Virginia. Accordingly, the Terms shall be governed by the laws of the state of Virginia, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. By accessing this website, you agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to the use of the website, including the purchase of any product, supplies or maintenance herefrom, shall be filed only in state or federal court located in Chesapeake, Virginia and you hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of such courts over any suit, action or proceeding arising out of the Terms.
General Provisions
Sihl reserves the right, without notice and in its sole discretion, to terminate your ability to use this website, and to block or prevent future access to and use of the website. If any provision of these Terms shall be deemed unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these terms and conditions and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. These Terms, including any applicable policy contained in this site, constitute the entire agreement between you and Sihl relating to the subject matter addressed herein.
Disclaimers
THIS WEBSITE, ANY PRODUCTS/GOODS, SERVICES OR SOFTWARE, AND ALL INFORMATION AND/OR CONTENT OF THE WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON- INFRINGMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE INFORMATION AND/ORCONTENT CONTAINED IN THIS WEBSITE IS BELIEVED TO BE ACCURATE AS OF THE DATE THE INFORMATION AND/OR CONTENT WAS ADDED TO THIS WEBSITE.
THE INFORMATION AND/OR CONTENT AT THIS WEBSITE MAY CONTAIN TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, INACCURACIES, OR OMISSIONS. SIHL RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CORRECT ANY ERRORS, INACCURACIES OR OMISSIONS OR UPDATE INFORMATION AND/OR CONTENT AT ANY TIME WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE. SIHL IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS OR OMISSIONS RELATING TO PRICING, TEXT OR PHOTOGRAPHY.
Changes or Modifications
Sihl reserves the right to change or modify any of the terms and conditions contained in these Terms of Use or any policy of the website, at any time and in its sole discretion. If Sihl decides to change its Terms of Use or a policy, Sihl will post a new version on its website and update the date. Any changes or modification will be effective upon posting of the revisions. Your continued use of this website following the posting of the changes or modifications will constitute your acceptance of such changes or modifications. You should frequently review these Terms of Use (including its date) and applicable policies from time-to-time to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of the website.
Privacy Policy
Sihl does not require visitors to supply personally identifiable information when accessing public areas of the site. When you browse the website, you do so anonymously, unless you have submitted an online registration form and selected a password or submitted your personal information in response to a site offer. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there, but we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged into our website through registration and a password or granted permission.
We do collect personally identifiable information when you register, access certain restricted site areas, place an order, request other information, or otherwise communicate with us about our offerings. Additionally, we may collect personally identifiable information when you register to attend a seminar, ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, submit an entry for a sweepstakes or other promotion, or you submit your personal information to Sihl for any other reason. From time to time, Sihl receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Sihl only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable industry privacy practices consistent with this policy and applicable laws. Personally identifiable information may be merged with other information Sihl already knows, such as whether you are a current Sihl customer, or whether you or your organization has had past contact with Sihl sales or marketing activities.
How we use the Information
Sihl collects this information for a variety of reasons, including Sihl's effort to inform you of product upgrades, special offers, and to ensure that you have access to information which is likely to be of interest to you. However, we do not sell or rent personally identifiable information to other organizations. On occasion, we may share personally identifiable information with an authorized Sihl dealer.
Your Choices
You may request, at any time, that the personally identifiable information you provide on a registration page or when updating your profile not be used for direct email marketing purposes by Sihl. The best way to do this is to select the option to modify your registration profile at www.sihlinc.com.. You will have the option to modify your email subscriptions or to remove your name entirely from all Sihl direct email marketing activities. If you do receive direct email marketing communication from Sihl, you will also receive options to remove your name from future mailings directly on the email. The options described on the email will be effective even if you are not a registered user of the website. If you need further help or have additional questions, please email us at www.sihlinc.com. Please provide your full name, email address and phone number so that we may address your concerns appropriately.
Sihl’s web sites may contain "links" to other non-Sihl web sites. It is also possible that non-Sihl web sites may link into Sihl web sites. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by those non-Sihl web sites.
Cookies
As is the case with many sites, when you visit our site or complete a registration form, we will place a "cookie" on your computer, which helps us identify you more quickly when you return. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know anything about you. They are used to identify you as a unique visitor to the site. We will not use "cookies" or other devices to follow your click stream on the Internet generally but will use them to determine which pages or information you find most useful or interesting at our own Web sites.
Most browsers permit you to refuse to accept a "cookie" offered by a Web site. You will not be denied access to any part of www.sihlinc.com because of your refusal to accept a "cookie," but your transactions through this Web site may be delayed due to the time it takes you to re-enter basic information necessary to complete a transaction.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
Due to the rapidly evolving nature of technologies Sihl uses to communicate with you, Sihl may occasionally update this privacy statement. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this privacy statement web page.
Questions or Suggestions
You should send any comments or questions regarding Sihl privacy practices on this site to us at www.sihlinc.com.
TechnologyDye Sub InksAqueous InkjetLatex InkjetSolvent InkjetUV Curable InkjetDigital Press (DT)
ApplicationsAdvertising & POSDye SublimationInterior DesignPhoto & ArtTechnical Solutions
© 2020 SIHL INC. |  All rights reserved  |  Sitemap  |  Privacy / Legal policy
